{
  "vulnerabilities": {
    "SQL_Injection": {
      "Difficulty": [
        [
          {
            "question": "How many unreleased products are there?",
            "answer": "0"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the total quantity of the unreleased products?",
            "answer": "null"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the most expensive product?",
            "answer": "10"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the total price of the inventory?",
            "answer": "1"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "How many total users are there?",
            "answer": "11"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the password for the on0xqm, as stored in the server database?",
            "answer": "ywyd9z"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the street address of on0xqm?",
            "answer": "ygjtzq"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the mobile number of the admin?",
            "answer": "9066928660"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the city of the admin?",
            "answer": "lav98m"
          }
        ]
      ]
    },
    "URL_rewriting": [
      {
        "question": "What is the current sessionID?",
        "answer": "ympYvS5sKcH40powTYzST8Ee6AjIdiNV"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the length of the current sessionID?",
        "answer": "32"
      }
    ],
    "XSS": [
      {
        "question": "What is the current sessionID?",
        "answer": "ympYvS5sKcH40powTYzST8Ee6AjIdiNV"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the length of the current sessionID?",
        "answer": "32"
      }
    ],
    "Authentication": [
      {
        "question": "What is the password for the admin user, as stored in the server database?",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the address of the admin?",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the provider number for the admin?",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the street address of the admin?",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the mobile number of the admin?",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the city of the admin?",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the password for the on0xqm, as stored in the server database?",
        "answer": "ywyd9z"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the street address of on0xqm?",
        "answer": "ygjtzq"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the mobile number of the admin?",
        "answer": "9066928660"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the city of the admin?",
        "answer": "lav98m"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the provider number for on0xqm",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the street address of on0xqm",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the mobile number of on0xqm",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      }
    ],
    "Paramater_tampering": [
      {
        "question": "What is the provider number for on0xqm",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the street address of on0xqm",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the mobile number of on0xqm",
        "answer": "sljpte"
      }
    ],
    "Admin_Console": [
      {
        "question": "How many total users are there?",
        "answer": "11"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the password for the on0xqm, as stored in the server database?",
        "answer": "ywyd9z"
      }
    ]
  }
}